Guide to the Centerbrook Architects and Planners Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Centerbrook Architects and Planners records
1963-2004
MS 1844
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
500.58
(1140 boxes)
The records consist of architectural and working/detail drawings of institutional, public, and private projects undertaken by Centerbrook Architects and Planners, LLC, as well as documentation of projects by pre-Centerbrook firms M/L/T/W Moore-Turnbull, Charles W. Moore Associates, and Moore Grover Harper. Relevant photographs, slides, correspondence, and newspaper clippings are included.
Centerbrook Architects
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Gift of Centerbrook Architects and Planners, LLC, 2005-2015.
Conditions Governing Access
Project numbers 639 (boxes N15-N25), 642 (boxes N1, N18, N25-N33), and 825 (boxes N1, N18, N25, N34-N48)require permission of the firm to access.
Original audiovisual materials, as well as preservation and duplicating masters, may not be played. Researchers must consult use copies, or if none exist must pay for a use copy, which is retained by the repository. Researchers wishing to obtain an additional copy of non-commercially produced items for their personal use should consult the ordering reproductions information on the Manuscripts and Archives web site.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of architectural and working/detail drawings of institutional, public, and private projects undertaken by Centerbrook Architects and Planners, LLC, as well as documentation of projects by pre-Centerbrook firms M/L/T/W Moore-Turnbull, Charles W. Moore Associates, and Moore Grover Harper. Relevant photographs, slides, correspondence, and newspaper clippings are included.
Biographical / Historical
In 1965, when Charles Moore became chair of the department of architecture in the Yale School of Art and Architecture, he left his firm, M/L/T/W, in Berkeley, California, and established a new firm in New Haven called MLTW/Moore-Turnbull. The ongoing reorganization of the firm resulted in two name changes (Charles W. Moore Associates; Moore Grover Harper) and was formally established as Centerbrook Architects after Moore returned to California to become head of the UCLA Department of Architecture. At Yale, Moore counted among his students three of the current Centerbrook partners: Jefferson B. Riley, Mark Simon, and Chad Floyd, as well as William Grover, who is now partner emeritus.
Currently led by four partners, Jefferson B. Riley, Mark Simon, Chad Floyd, and James Childress, Centerbrook's design services encompass project management, planning, interior design, sculpture, landscape and site design, industrial design, furniture and lighting design, fund raising support, and graphic design. Centerbrook has garnered more than 325 design awards, and in 1998, the American Institute of Architects recognized Centerbrook with its prestigious National Firm Award.
Founded during a decade of oil embargoes and price spikes, Centerbrook initially designed energy-conserving, passive-solar homes, including an underground house in Vermont, a partner's passive solar home, and a demonstration home for NASA. Two major projects, the Northeast's largest active solar building for the Connecticut National Guard and a museum for Williams College, helped the practice to grow steadily from a focus on residential design to large scale projects and planning for cities and colleges. Remaining veteran practitioners of "green" architecture, the firm has incorporated affordable conservation into more than 50 projects, many of which are LEED certified.
Since 1975, the firm has continued to diversify its portfolio with work in academia, the arts, business, science, religious architecture, and residential housing. In the mid-1970s, two of the firm's clients became significant mainstays of its practice: Cold Spring Harbor Laboratory on Long Island and Quinnipiac University in Hamden, Connecticut. Since that time, Centerbrook continued to design numerous master plans, buildings, campuses, and renovations for these two institutions.
Centerbrook has worked on numerous projects at Yale University, among them Kroon Hall with Hopkins Architects, the Cullman-Heyman Tennis Center, and the Yale Child Study Center. It has designed multiple buildings at other campuses as well, such as Dartmouth, the University of Colorado, Phillips Academy Andover, Pomfret School, Quinnipiac University, the University of Connecticut, and the University of Texas.
Firm history by David Holahan, Centerbrook Architects and Planners
Arrangement
The materials are arranged by accession. Letters in front of box numbers in the project index refer to the accession in which the material was received.
Other Finding Aids
For a list of projects and the boxes in which project materials are located, please consult the Project Index.
List of Projects in Collection
Abramson House, [suburb of] Washington, DC
Acheson House, Essex, CT
Adams House, Madison, CT
Air Rights Parking Garage [66 York Street, Sixty-Six York Street], New Haven, CT
Akron Cascade Superblock, Akron, OH
Alcoa Prefabricated Housing
Ambro House, East Hampton, CT
American Shakespeare Theatre, Stratford, CT
Amusement Park, NJ
Anderson Housing Development, Springfield, MA
Anderson Towers, Springfield, MA
Antioch College, South Hall, Yellow Springs, OH
Backstreet Restaurant [Oranzo], New Haven, CT
Baldwin House, Essex, CT
Baldwin Lieberman Segaloff Law Offices, New Haven, CT
Bankes House, Brewster, NY
Barber House, Guilford, CT
Barnes House, Essex, CT
Berger House, Roxbury, CT
Best Products show for the Museum of Modern Art, New York, NY
Boas House, Stinson Beach, CA
Bonham House, Boulder Creek, CA
Brown University: Pembroke dormitories, Providence, RI
Buchanan House, Killingworth, CT
Budge House, Healdsburg, CA
Budin Apartment, New York, NY
Budin House and alterations, Copake, NY
Burke House, pool house, and unbuilt design, Greenwich, CT
Burns House, Los Angeles, CA
Carmel Knolls Housing, Carmel, CA
Castle House, Stonington, CT
Cedar Rapids Museum of Arts, Cedar Rapids, IA
Chester Diversified Properties, Chester, CT
Church Street South Redevelopment, New Haven, CT
Citizens Federal Savings and Loan Building, San Francisco, CA
Clark House, Old Lyme, CT
Clocktower, Middletown, CT
Colby College Student Center, Waterville, ME
Cold Spring Harbor Laboratory: Airslie, Cold Spring Harbor, NY
Cold Spring Harbor Laboratory: Chancellor's House, Cold Spring Harbor, NY
Cold Spring Harbor Laboratory: Grace Auditorium, Cold Spring Harbor, NY
Cold Spring Harbor Laboratory: Jones Laboratory, Cold Spring Harbor, NY
Cold Spring Harbor Laboratory: Neuroscience Center, Cold Spring Harbor, NY
Cold Spring Harbor Laboratory: Sammis Hall, Cold Spring Harbor, NY
Cold Spring Harbor Laboratory: Waste Water Treatment Plant, Cold Spring Harbor, NY
Consulate General's House, New Haven, CT
Cook House [unbuilt], Great Falls, VA
Cornuelle House
County Federal Savings Bank, Greens Farms, CT
Court Street Center, Cincinnati, OH
Cranbury Road Housing, Hightstown, NJ
Crowell House I, VT
Dartmouth College, Tuck School of Business, Byrne Hall, Hanover, NH
Dartmouth College, Tuck School of Business, Chase House Renovation, Hanover, NH
Dartmouth College, Tuck School of Business, Dormitory, Hanover, NH
Dartmouth College, Tuck School of Business, Murdough Hall Renovation, Hanover, NH
Dartmouth College, Tuck School of Business, Stell Hall Renovation, Hanover, NH
Dauntless Yacht Club, Essex, CT
Dayton Kiwanis Floating Fountain, Dayton, OH
Dayton Riverdesign, Dayton, OH
Dayton Riverfront Park, Dayton, OH
East Hampton Library and Multicultural Center, East Hampton, CT
East Lyme Library and Community Center, East Lyme, CT
Eastern Kentucky Housing Development Corporation, Whitesburg, KY
Eisenstein House, Midwest
Elliott-Gruen House, Ligonier, PA
Elmwood Park Revitalization, Roanoke, VA
Encosystems Spec House, Essex, CT
Essex Point, Deep River, CT
Farber House renovation, Woodbridge, CT
Fremont City Gall Competition, Fremont, CA
Gagarin House, Peru, VT
Gazebo for House & Garden Magazine
Goodman House, Montauk, NY
Grace Auditorium, Cold Spring Harbor Laboratory, Cold Spring Harbor, NY
Gringer Apartment, New York, NY
Gross House, Hartland, VT
"Guest House in the Country", CT
Gund Investment Corporation Offices, Phases I and II, Princeton, NJ
Halprin House, Sea Ranch, CA
Harrison House, Santa Barbara, CA
Heritage Harbor, Annapolis, MD
Hindman Pool, New Zion, KY
Hines House, Sea Ranch, CA
Hood Museum of Art, Dartmouth College, Hanover, NH
House Beautiful House [see also Burlington House, Job 292], Burlington, CT
"House in the Berkshires", Alford, MA
"House in the Country", CT
"House Near New York" and addition, NJ
Hubbard House, Corral de Tierra, CA
Huntington Station Plaza, Huntington, NY
Indian Springs Ranch, Salinas, CA
Ingenium, Springfield, MA
Ireland House, Martha's Vineyard, MA
Isham House, Sagaponack, NY
Jaffe House II and Pool House, Guilford, CT
Jewell House, Orinda, CA
Jobson House, Paolo Colorado Canyon, CA
Johnson House, Canaan, NY
Johnson House, Sea Ranch, CA
Jones House additions and renovations, Stamford, CT
Kansas City Urban Graphics, Kansas City, MO
Kaplan House [see also Connecticut House, Job 307; Kaplan II, Job 396], Chester, CT
Karas House, Monterey, CA
Kingsmill on the James Housing, Williamsburg, VA
Kissam House addition
Klotz Development, West Hampton, NY
Klotz House
Klugman House, Guilford, CT
Knisely House I [vacation house], NY
Knisely House II, NY
Koizim House, Westport, CT
Krementz Studio, New York, NY
Kuhio Shores Mauka, Kauai, HI
Lawrence House, Sea Ranch, CA
Lawrence University: Wriston Art Center, Appleton, WI
Lenz Winery, Peconic, NY
Les Halles competition, Paris, France
Levin House, Little Falls, NY
Lone Hill Housing, San Jose, CA
"Long View", New England
Lovejoy Fountain, Portland, OR
Malibu Apartments, Malibu, CA
Manville Apartment/Friday Apartment, New York, NY
Mapplewood Terrace Low-Income Housing, Middletown, CT
May House, Old Saybrook, CT
McElrath House, Santa Cruz, CA
McKee House
McKim House, Fishers Island, NY
McClintock Laboratory, Cold Spring Harbor Laboratory, Cold Spring Harbor, NY
Middletown Inn and Renewal, Middletown, CT
Middletown Public Elderly Housing, Middletown, CT
Miller, Peter House and addition, Burlington, VT
Minnesota History Center competition, St. Paul, MN
Monte Vista addition, Monterey, CA
Moore [Charles W.] House, Centerbrook, CT
Moore House, New Haven, CT
Murray House, Cambridge, MA
Naff House, Pajaro Dunes, CA
NASA Project Tech House [Technology Utilization House]
Nauticus [The National Maritime Center], Norfolk, VA
Navy Lodge Modular Housing, Newport, RI and New London, CT
Neurogen Corporation, Branford, CT
New Haven College Student Housing, New Haven, CT
New Haven Dance Center, New Haven, CT
No Bottom Development, Westerly, RI
North House, Essex, CT
North Spec House, Essex, CT
Norwich Armory, Norwich, CT
Ocala House [Amrep Foundation], Orlando, FL
Old Farm, Mount Holly, Westhampton, NJ
Orlando Housing [Amrep Foundation], Orlando, FL
Orono Housing, Orono, ME
Otus House, Berkeley, CA
Owen Brown Village, Columbia, MD
Parc de la Villette competition, Paris, France
Paumanack Manor Housing for the Elderly
Pearson House addition, Branford, CT
Percarpio House, Guilford, CT
Peterson House, Tacoma, WA
Pfizer Plant: Main Gate, Groton, CT
Pfizer Plant: Master Plan, Groton, CT
Pfizer Plant: South Gate, Groton, CT
Piazza d'Italia, New Orleans, LA
Pittsburgh Fountain, Pittsburgh, PA
"The Place of Houses" [book drawings and associated material]
Pond House, New England Island
Psychoanalytic Associates, Los Angeles, CA
Quanaduck Cove, Stonington, CT
Quinnipiac University: Carl Hansen Student Center [see also Student Union renovation], Hamden, CT
Quinnipiac University: Computer Center, Hamden, CT
Quinnipiac University: Dining Hall and Servery Complex, Hamden, CT
Quinnipiac University: Dormitory Complex, Hamden, CT
Quinnipiac University: Dormitory Village, Hamden, CT
Quinnipiac University: Echlin Health Sciences Center, Hamden, CT
Quinnipiac University: Student Union renovation, Hamden CT
Quinnipiac University: Suntraps, Hamden, CT
Raval Planning Study [Senior Citizens Housing Committee], Huntington, NY
Ray House
Reebok Corporate Campus, Stoughton, MA
Reid House I, Cleveland Heights, OH
Reid House II, West Falmouth, MA
Rensselaer Polytechnic Institute, Folson Library Fountain, Troy, NY
Riley House I ["Dunk House"], Guilford, CT
River-Dale Consumer Outlet and Travel Center, West Springfield, MA
Riverdesign Springfield, Springfield, MA
Roanoke "Design '79", Roanoke, VA
Roanoke Hotel and Convention Center, Roanoke, VA
Roanoke Library Addition, Roanoke, VA
Roanoke Market Building, Roanoke, VA
Roanoke Parking Garages, Roanoke, VA
Roanoke Transportation Center, Roanoke, VA
Rocky Neck Corporate Park, Rocky Neck, CT
Rosko House I and II, Southampton, NY
Ross-Lacy House, Sherman, CT
Rottschafer House, Guilford, CT
Rowe House and guest house, Essex, CT
Rubenstein House, MD
Rudolph House I, Captiva Island, FL
Rudolph House II, Williamstown, MA
Rush House, Sea Ranch, CA
Savin Rock Urban Renewal Project #2, West Haven, CT
Saz House, Woods Hole, MA
Schaffer House, Branford, CT
Scheuer House, Larchmont, NY
Schrader Development, Guilford, CT
Schub House, Sag Harbor, NY
Sea Ranch Condominium #1 and miscellaneous material, Sea Ranch, CA
Sea Ranch Spec House, Sea Ranch, CA
Seattle Civic Center Fountain Competition, Seattle, WA
Shattuck House, Guilford, CT
Shinefield House, Sea Ranch, CA
Slater House, Hamburg Cove, CT
Slater House, Stinson Beach, CA
Solar Heated House - Experimental [Solar Spec House]
Southern Illinois University, Carbondale, IL
Springfield Crafts Village, Springfield, MA
St. Simon Sales Center [Xanadune], St. Simon Island, CA
Stanwood House, Bloomfield, CT
Stern House, Woodbridge, CT
Stern Toole & Shaw Office, New Haven, CT
Striar Jewish Community Center, Stoughton, MA
Swan House, Southhold, NY
Swanson House I and II, Cherry Hills, Chicago, IL
Talbert House, Oakland, CA
Taplin House, Amesbury, MA
Taylor Town Houses, Norwalk, CT
Taylor-Walker Residence, CT
Tempchin House, Bethesda, MD
Tortilla City Hall [student project]
Tower East, New Haven, CT
Tower One, New Haven, CT
Tri-Pac Housing, Vernon, CT
University of California Arts Center Competition
University of California, Santa Barbara; Faculty Club, Santa Barbara, CA
University of California, Santa Cruz: Kresge College [College Six], Santa Cruz, CA
University of Connectucut Staff Housing, Storrs, CT
University of Toledo, Honors Housing and Academic Center, Toledo, OH
Villa del Monte, Seaside, CA
Wallingford Railroad Station [Yale class project], Wallingford, CT
Washburn Houses, Pacific Grove, CA
Watkins Glen Development Plan ["Watkins Glen Tomorrow"], Watkins Glen, NY
Watkins Glen Marina, Watkins Glen, NY
Watkins Glen Pier and Pavilion, Watkins Glen, NY
Watkins Glen Seneca Market, Watkins Glen, NY
Watkins Glen State Park [including Timespell], Watkins Glen, NY
Weltner House and pottery studio, Haddam, CT
Wernick Offices [unbuilt], Bristol, CT
West Plaza Condominium, Coronado, CA
Weyerhauser Demonstration House, Kansas City, MO
Whitman Village, Huntington, NY
Williams College Museum of Art, Phase I and II, Williamstown, MA
Williams College: Charles Moore exhibit, Williamstown, MA
Wolfe [Robert T.] Housing for the Elderly, New Haven, CT
Wooster Street Housing Redevelopment Project B-19, New Haven, CT
Worcester Polytechnic Institute [WPI] Campus Plan, Worcester, MA
Wrexham Hall
Xanadune, St. Simon Island, GA
Yale Mathematics Building Competition, New Haven, CT
Yurko House
Architecture; Architecture -- Designs and plans; Architects; Centerbrook Architects
- Project records, Circa 1963-2004
  General
  For a list of projects and the boxes in which project materials are located, please consult the Project Index.
  - "House Near New York", 1973-1976
    Scope and Contents
    Job location: New Jersey
    - Manuscript Materials (Box J28)
    - Sketches (Box J21)
    - Schematic/Design Development Drawings (Box J20, Box J24–J25)
    - Landscape/Site Drawings (Box J23)
    - As-Built/Record Drawings (Box J26–J27)
    - Presentation Drawings (Box J27–J28)
    - Mechanical/Electrical/HVAC Drawings (Box J22)
    - Photographs (Box J28)
    - Slides (Box J28)
    - Architectural/Structural Drawings (Box J20, Box J22, Box J24–J26)
  - "House Near New York" expansion, 1987
    - Manuscript Materials (Box J28)
    - Architectural/Structural Drawings (Box J29)
    - Photographs (Box J28)
    - Slides (Box J28)
  - "Return to Humanism" [promotional brochure for firm]
    - Manuscript Materials (Box A23)
  - Abramson House, 1982
    Job location: Suburb of Washington, D.C.
    - Manuscript Materials (Box E1–E2)
    - Sketches (Box E3–E4, Box E7)
    - Schematic/Design Development Drawings (Box E8)
    - As-Built/Record Drawings (Box E9)
    - Presentation Drawings (Box E4, Box E10–E13)
    - Architectural/Structural Drawings (Box E5–E6)
    - Photographs (Box E1–E2)
    - Slides (Box E1–E2)
  - Acheson House, 1987
    Job location: Essex, CT
    - Manuscript Materials (Box K3)
    - Schematic/Design Development Drawings (Box K1)
    - Presentation Drawings (Box K2)
    - Architectural/Structural Drawings (Box K2)
    - Photographs (Box K3)
    - Slides (Box K3)
  - Adams House, 1986
    Job location: Madison, CT
    - Manuscript Materials (Box H1)
    - Sketches (Box H3–H6)
    - Presentation Drawings (Box H6)
    - Architectural/Structural Drawings (Box H2)
    - Photographs (Box H1)
    - Slides (Box H1)
  - Air Rights Parking Garage [aka 66 York Street, Sixty-Six York Street], 1986
    Job location: New Haven, CT
    - Manuscript Materials (Box K5)
    - Schematic/Design Development Drawings (Box K44)
    - Presentation Drawings (Folder K45)
    - Architectural/Structural Drawings (Box K43)
    - Slides (Box K5)
  - Akron Cascade Superblock, 1966
    Job location: Akron, OH
    - Manuscript Materials (Box K4)
    - Sketches (Box K4)
    - Photographs (Box K4)
  - Alcoa Prefabricated Housing, 1965
    - Manuscript Materials (Box K5)
    - Sketches (Box K5–K6)
    - Presentation Drawings (Box K6)
  - Ambro House, 1972-1973
    Job location: East Hampton, NY
    - Schematic/Design Development Drawings (Box N5)
    - Architectural/Structural Drawings (Box N5)
  - American Shakespeare Theatre, 1969
    Job location: Stratford, CT
    - Manuscript Materials (Box E55)
    - Sketches (Box B2–B3)
    - Schematic/Design Development Drawings (Box B3)
    - Landscape/Site Drawings (Box B3)
    - Presentation Drawings (Box B2, Box E55)
    - Photographs (Box E55)
    - Negatives (Box B3, Box E55)
  - Amusement Park, 1985
    - Presentation Drawings (Box I1)
  - Anderson Housing Development, 1973
    Job location: Springfield, MA
    - Sketches (Box B1–I1)
    - Schematic/Design Development Drawings (Box B1)
    - Landscape/Site Drawings (Box B1–I1)
    - Presentation Drawings (Box G1)
    - Photographs (Box I1)
    - Negatives (Box I1)
  - Anderson Towers, 1966
    - As-Built/Record Drawings (Box B4)
  - Antioch College, South Hall, 1972
    Job location: Yellow Springs, OH
    - Schematic/Design Development Drawings (Box M9)
  - Backstreet Restaurant (Oranzo), 1980
    - Manuscript Materials (Box E15)
    - Sketches (Box E14)
    - Schematic/Design Development Drawings (Box E14)
    - Architectural/Structural Drawings (Box E14)
    - Slides (Box E15)
  - Baer, Morley photographs (notebook)
    - Photographs (Box E15)
  - Baldwin House, 1985
    - Manuscript Materials (Box G2)
    - Presentation Drawings (Box G33)
    - Architectural/Structural Drawings (Box G33)
    - Photographs (Box G2)
    - Slides (Box G2)
  - Baldwin Lieberman Segaloff Law Offices, 1976
    - Manuscript Materials (Box D1)
    - Sketches (Box D1, Box D16)
    - Schematic/Design Development Drawings (Box D16)
    - Architectural/Structural Drawings (Box D16)
    - Photographs (Box D1)
    - Slides (Box D1)
  - Bankes House, 1967
    Job location: Brewster, NY
    - Sketches (Box B4)
  - Barber House, 1975
    Job location: Guilford, CT
    - Manuscript Materials (Box J2)
    - Sketches (Box J2)
    - Schematic/Design Development Drawings (Box J3)
    - Presentation Drawings (Box J1, Box J3)
    - Architectural/Structural Drawings (Box J3)
    - Slides (Box J2)
  - Barnes House, 1974
    - Manuscript Materials (Box M1)
    - Presentation Drawings (Box M5)
    - Architectural/Structural Drawings (Box M5)
    - Photographs (Box M1)
  - Berger House, 1990
    Job location: Roxbury, CT
    - Manuscript Materials (Box F28)
    - Schematic/Design Development Drawings (Box F44–F45)
    - As-Built/Record Drawings (Box F43–F45)
    - Presentation Drawings (Box F31)
    - Slides (Box F28)
  - Best Products show for the Museum of Modern Art, 1978
    Job location: New York, NY
    - Presentation Drawings (Box N3)
    - Photographs (Box N3)
  - Boas House, 1967
    Job location: Stinson Beach, CA
    - Architectural/Structural Drawings (Box B5)
  - Bonham House, 1962
    Job location: Boulder Creek, CA
    - Manuscript Materials (Box N2)
    - Sketches (Box N2)
    - Photographs (Box N2)
  - Brown University: Pembroke dormitories, 1969
    Job location: Providence, RI
    - Manuscript Materials (Box N3)
    - Sketches (Box N3)
    - Photographs (Box N3)
    - Slides (Box N3)
  - Buchanan House, 1992
    Job location: Killingworth, CT
    - Manuscript Materials (Box P4)
    - Sketches (Box P2)
    - Landscape/Site Drawings (Box P2)
    - Presentation Drawings (Box P3)
    - Architectural/Structural Drawings (Box P3)
    - Photographs (Box P4)
  - Budge House, 1967
    Job location: Healdsburg, CA
    - Manuscript Materials (Box N4)
    - Photographs (Box N4)
  - Budin Apartment I, 1991
    - Manuscript Materials (Box P6)
    - Architectural/Structural Drawings (Box P5)
    - Slides (Box P6)
  - Budin House, 1982
    Job location: Copake, NY
    - Sketches (Box E17)
    - Schematic/Design Development Drawings (Box E20)
    - Presentation Drawings (Box E16)
    - Architectural/Structural Drawings (Box E16, Box E18–E19, Box E21)
    - Photographs (Box E2)
    - Slides (Box E2)
  - Budin House alterations, 1992
    - Manuscript Materials (Box P6)
    - Architectural/Structural Drawings (Box E22–E23)
  - Burke House and poolhouse, 1990
    Job location: Greenwich, CT
    - Manuscript Materials (Box I24–I27)
    - Sketches (Box I28–I30, Box I32)
    - Schematic/Design Development Drawings (Box I29–I30)
    - Presentation Drawings (Box I28)
    - Architectural/Structural Drawings (Box I31–I32)
    - Photographs (Box I27)
    - Slides (Box I27)
  - Burke House: unbuilt design, 1984-1986
    - Manuscript Materials (Box I24–I27)
    - Sketches (Box I20–I21)
    - Schematic/Design Development Drawings (Box I21–I22)
    - Architectural/Structural Drawings (Box I21–I23)
    - Photographs (Box I27)
    - Slides (Box I27)
  - Burns House, 1972-1974
    Job location: Los Angeles, CA
    - Manuscript Materials (Box C1)
    - Architectural/Structural Drawings (Box C53)
    - Mechanical/Electrical/HVAC Drawings (Box C53)
    - Slides (Box C1)
  - Carmel Knolls Housing, 1964
    Job location: Carmel, CA
    - Manuscript Materials (Box N4)
    - Presentation Drawings (Box N4)
  - Castle House, 1990-1992
    Job location: Stonington, CT
    - Manuscript Materials (Box P11–P12)
    - Sketches (Box P9)
    - Schematic/Design Development Drawings (Box P9)
    - Landscape/Site Drawings (Box P7)
    - As-Built/Record Drawings (Box P8)
    - Presentation Drawings (Box P10)
    - Architectural/Structural Drawings (Box P8)
    - Photographs (Box P11)
    - Slides (Box P11)
  - Cedar Rapids Museum of Arts, 1984
    Job location: Cedar Rapids, IA
    - Manuscript Materials (Box N2, Box G3–G10)
    - Sketches (Box G10, Box G34)
    - Schematic/Design Development Drawings (Box G36–G37, Box G41–G42)
    - As-Built/Record Drawings (Box G38)